Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Administrative Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Richard V. Szary, head of Manuscripts and Archives, records, 1991-2006; Accession 2007-A-134
  - Manuscripts and Archives
    - Connections
      - Open House, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 462)
      - MSSA Research Gateway, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 463)
      - Seth Conference, 1994 October (Box 7, Folder 464)
      - Seth Conference, 1995 October (Box 7, Folder 465)
    - Exhibits
      - Gandhi
        - Exhibits - general translation and labels, circa 1995 (Box 7, Folder 466)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 467)
        - Exhibit Materials, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 468)
        - Exhibit, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 469 - 471)
        - Exhibit labels, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 472)
        - Exhibit, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 473 - 474)
        - Exhibit - background materials, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 475)
        - 1997 (Box 7, Folder 476)
        - 1999 (Box 7, Folder 477)
      - Whiffenpoofs, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 478)
      - Brewster exhibit, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 479)
      - PUBPROG - Exhibit documentation, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 480)
      - Elms and Magnolias, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 481)
      - Hoak Exhibit, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 482)
      - External: Palestinian posters, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 483)
      - Traveling - Rand - College of St. Rose, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 484)
      - Class of 1955, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 485)
    - Collection Development
      - Collection Development Working Group, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 486)
      - Retreat, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 490)
      - Gift Agreements, Undated (Box 8, Folder 491)
      - Manuscripts and Archives Collection Development policy, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 494)
      - Appraisers, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 495)
    - Collection Management and Reader Services
      - Beinecke transfers, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 496)
      - Patron/Circulation Control System (PCCS), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 497)
      - Security and special concerns, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 498)
      - Copy negatives - digitization, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 499)
      - Microfilm Readers, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 500)
      - Microfilm Distribution-sales by MSSA, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 501)
      - Microfilm for users: Datamix, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 502)
      - Photocopy operation - microfilm readers and printers, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 503)
      - Microfilming RLG grant, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 504)
      - Facilities - LSF, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 505)
      - Vault list - Manuscripts, 1988-1991 (Box 8, Folder 506 - 507)
      - Report on space and equipment requirements, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 508)
      - Collections management, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 509)
      - Collections management and reader services working groups, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 510)
      - Hold area, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 511)
      - Reader services and reference assistance, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 512)
      - Collections storage - audio and video tapes, circa 1990 (Box 8, Folder 513)
      - Collections storage - Yale publications, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 514)
      - Commercial Storage, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 515)
      - Facsimile reproduction, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 516)
      - Insurance valuation, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 517)
      - Preservation - microfilm duplication, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 518)
      - Preservation supplies, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 519)
      - Shipping, 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 520)
      - Scanning and imaging for researchers, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 521)
      - Microform publications: Scholarly Resources, 1996-2000 (Box 8, Folder 522)
      - Yale-Yale-Yale, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 523)
    - Collection Areas
      - African, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 524)
      - Miscellaneous Collections, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 525)
      - Pamphlets, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 526)
      - South Asian studies committee, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 527)
      - Architectural archives program, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 528)
      - Arts Collecting, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 529)
      - Contemporary Medical Care and Health Policy, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 530)
      - International Affairs, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 531)
      - Middle East Collections, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 532)
      - New Haven labor archives, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 533)
      - Nursing, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 534)
      - Legal
        - Collaboration with Law School, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 535)
        - 2ndCircuit Court of Appeals CD, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 536)
        - Attorney-client privilege, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 537)
      - African Collection, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 538)
      - Faculty Papers, 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 539)
      - German posters: Thomas Hill, 1992-2002 (Box 8, Folder 540)
      - Dealers - Camden Books - I. Fisher, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 541)
      - Arts, circa 1995 (Box 8, Folder 542)
      - Aviation history, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 543)
      - Faculty papers, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 544)
      - Human Rights Initiative, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 545)
      - Judaic Collection, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 546)
      - Slavic and E. European, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 547)
    - Projects
      - Project lists, 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 548)
      - Card catalog reformatting, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 549)
      - Latin American Manuscripts, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 550)
      - Making of America II, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 551)
      - Microforms Transfer to Microtext Reading Room, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 552)
      - New Haven City Room, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 553)
      - National Historical Publications and records Commission (NHPRC) fellow 1994-95 application (Box 8, Folder 554)
      - ORBIS OPAC screens, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 555)
      - Paris Peace Conference - 75thanniversary symposium, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 556)
      - PCCS, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 557)
      - Posture photos, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 558)
      - Presidential records project, 1991-1995 (Box 9, Folder 559)
      - Projects on Greater China, 1982-1995 (Box 9, Folder 560)
      - Registers in electronic format, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 561)
      - Retrospective description project, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 562)
      - RLG Symposium Q, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 563)
      - Shredder analysis, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 564)
      - South Asian Studies Committee, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 565)
      - United Nations Archives, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 566)
      - United Nations Workstation, 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 567)
      - Yale/China Photograph Archive (Tawny Ryan Nelb), 1982 (Box 9, Folder 568)
      - Latin American Manuscripts - Gale, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 569)
      - SGML Finding Aids Project
        - Finding Aids Project, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 570)
        - EAD-Text deployers, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 571)
        - Server Committee, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 572)
        - SGML at Yale -roles, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 573)
        - Encoded Archival Description (EAD) -Yale Finding Aid Project (YFAP) -P.H. -Visit, 1996 April (Box 9, Folder 574)
        - YFAP, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 575)
        - EAD -YFAP systems Group, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 576)
        - YFAP -Text Deployment Group, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 577)
        - Server requirements, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 578)
        - Open Text, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 579)
        - WordPerfect SGML, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 580)
        - SoftQuad, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 581)
        - EAD -visitors and inquiries, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 582)
        - EAD -Outreach, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 583)
        - BASIS, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 584)
        - EBT, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 585)
        - Exceed, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 586)
      - Web Committee
        - Web page draft, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 587)
        - Feedback (1stedition), 1996 (Box 9, Folder 588)
        - Draft web site feedback -departmental, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 589)
        - Final edits (1stedition), 1996 (Box 9, Folder 590)
        - Committee: MSSA home page texts, styles, and software, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 591)
        - Registration (1stedition), 1996 (Box 9, Folder 592)
        - Second edition ideas and corrections (1stedition), 1996 (Box 9, Folder 593)
        - 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 594)
        - Design, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 595)
        - Collection use and services (texts), circa 1995 (Box 9, Folder 596)
        - University Archives (texts), circa 1995 (Box 9, Folder 597)
        - Hours and location, circa 1995 (Box 9, Folder 598)
        - Directory, circa 1995 (Box 9, Folder 599)
      - American Jewish Society for Service (AJSS) Papers
        - Acknowledgment, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 600)
        - Arrangement and Description, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 601)
        - Preliminary inventories and background materials, circa 1991 (Box 9, Folder 602)
        - Processing Plan, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 603)
        - Shredding statistics, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 604)
        - Supplies, circa 1995 (Box 9, Folder 605)
        - Tasks, circa 1995 (Box 9, Folder 606)
      - Brewster Presidential Records
        - Afro-American Studies request, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 607)
        - Data Base Proposal, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 608)
        - Descriptions (sample) of presidential records, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 609)
        - RU 22 workbook, circa 1991 (Box 9, Folder 610)
        - Brewster Exhibit maintenance and administration, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 611)
        - General collection documentation, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 612)
        - GK's requests, 1992-1996 (Box 9, Folder 613)
        - Goals and objectives, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 614)
        - Job description, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 615)
        - Layout, Undated (Box 9, Folder 616)
        - MSSA General Information and Research Use (Restrictions), 1990 (Box 9, Folder 617)
        - Materials Signed-Out, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 618)
        - Original Collection Status -Date Listing, circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 619)
        - Original Collection Status -Subject Listing, circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 620)
        - Plans (copies), 1992 (Box 9, Folder 621)
        - Preservation, circa 1991 (Box 9, Folder 622)
        - Princeton Report (return to Mark Bailey), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 623)
        - Project proposal and initial documentation, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 624)
        - Processing Guide, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 625)
        - Processing Plan -Accession List (Box 9, Folder 626)
        - Processing Plan, Others originals, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 627)
        - Published Register, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 628)
        - Records collection notes, circa 1991 (Box 9, Folder 629)
        - Record Units, circa 1991 (Box 9, Folder 630)
        - Brewster restriction, circa 1991 (Box 9, Folder 631)
        - Shredding file and statistics, circa 1991 (Box 9, Folder 632)
        - Supplies, finances, 1991-1995 (Box 9, Folder 633)
        - Subsequent incoming materials, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 634)
        - Brewster tasks, circa 1991 (Box 9, Folder 635)
        - Term reports and related documentation, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 636)
        - Subject and date listings (Box 9, Folder 637)
        - Articles about Brewster and Yale, 1964-1991 (Box 10, Folder 638)
        - Biographical information, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 639)
        - Articles from Public Information File, 1964-1977 (Box 10, Folder 640)
        - Doonesbury (Bull Tales), 1970-1989 (Box 10, Folder 641)
        - Background notes and reports, 1973-1995 (Box 10, Folder 642)
        - Administration of the Brewster years, 1963-1977 (Box 10, Folder 643)
        - Quotes, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 645)
        - "Long Live the King's Yale: How Kingman Brewster's University Survived and Thrived in the 1960s", Jeremy Weinberg's Senior Essay on Brewster's Presidency, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 646)
        - Brewster Papers, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 647)
      - Public Services
        - Public Services meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 648 - 649)
        - 1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 650)
        - Chadwyck-Healey, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 651)
        - Public and reader services restructuring, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 652)
        - Permission to Publish, Copyright, Facsimile, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 653)
        - User Presentation Language study, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 654)
        - User survey, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 655 - 656)
        - Reference consultant, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 657)
        - Issues: digital imaging, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 658)
        - 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 659)
      - Systems
        - Computer data, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 660)
        - Information Technology - planning and budget, 1993-1995 (Box 10, Folder 661)
        - Departmental network, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 662)
        - Information technology planning, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 663)
        - Systems planning - equipment, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 664)
        - Systems planning - network, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 665)
        - Manuscripts and Archives (MSSA) Automation, 1988-1992 (Box 10, Folder 666)
        - MSSA - Automation planning, 1988-1996 (Box 10, Folder 667)
        - Automation - training, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 668)
        - Automation - YCC charges, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 669)
        - Systems priorities, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 670)
  - Video Archive for Holocaust Testimonies (VAHT)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 672)
    - Videotape Preservation, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 673)
    - Outside Production: Story Channel, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 674)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 675)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 676)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 677)
    - 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 678)
    - 1988 (Box 10, Folder 679)
    - 1989 (Box 10, Folder 680)
    - Museum of Jewish Heritage, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 681)
    - Archivist/Coordinator, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 682)
    - Postings, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 683)
    - Archives Assistant - D, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 684)
    - 1990 (Box 10, Folder 685)
    - 1991 (Box 11, Folder 686)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 687)
    - Spielberg, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 688)
    - Video Archive, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 689)
    - Video Preservation, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 691)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 692)
    - Genocide Research Program, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 693)
  - Research Libraries Group
    - Mailbox inventory, computer file (XML)
    - General, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 694)
    - Archival Resources, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 695)
    - Primary Sources Advisory Council (PSAC), 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 696)
    - Primary Sources Symposium, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 697)
    - Primary Sources Advisory Council (PSAC), 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 698 - 699)
    - Primary Sources Forum
      - 1995 Mar 3 (Box 11, Folder 700)
      - Advisory Group
        - 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 701)
        - Background documents, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 702)
        - Notes and thoughts, circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 703)
        - LISTSERV and other dissemination, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 704)
    - Primary Sources Advisory Group SHARES recommendations, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 705)
    - PSAG CONFER documentation, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 706)
    - PSAC, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 707)
    - RLIN, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 708)
  - Manuscripts and Archives
    - Budget and Accounting
      - 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 709)
      - Budget, 1990-1997 (Box 11, Folder 710)
      - Budget and finances: Project X, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 711)
      - Financial monitoring, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 713)
      - Sales of supplies, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 714)
      - Revenue operation, 1995-1998 (Box 11, Folder 715)
      - Student wage budget, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 716)
      - Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 717)
      - MSSA Budget - Financial Statements, 1968-1973 (Box 11, Folder 718 - 721)
      - Notes on financial statements, wages, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 722)
      - Wage projections, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 723)
      - Notes on financial statements, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 724)
    - Development
      - Planning and development, 1990-1996 (Box 11, Folder 726)
      - University acknowledgments, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 727)
      - Development plans, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 728)
      - Cowles, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 734)
      - Renovation of public areas, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 735)
    - Facilities
      - Library Shelving Facility (LSF), 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 736)
      - LSF Bar coding, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 737)
      - SML: Chapel, circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 738)
      - Cowles Reference Center, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 739 - 740)
      - Reference center renovation, 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 741)
      - SML Renovation - Phase II, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 742)
      - Yale University Library (YUL), MSSA alteration and building maintenance requests, 1990 November (Box 11, Folder 743)
      - Alteration requests, 1991-1994 (Box 11, Folder 744 - 745)
      - Asbestos, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 746)
      - Collection storage, 1989-1994 (Box 11, Folder 747)
      - Emergency Procedures 1.3.3, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 748)
      - Fire drill, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 749)
      - Renovation
        - Memorabilia Room and Exhibit corridor, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 750)
        - Restoration of paintings and busts, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 751)
      - Security/Theft, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 752)
      - Security incident, 1992 June 22 (Box 11, Folder 753)
      - Facilities - University warehouse, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 754)
    - Space
      - Space planning, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 755)
      - Space study, 1988-1991 (Box 12, Folder 756)
      - Statistics, 1991-1995 (Box 12, Folder 757)
      - Collection storage study, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 758)
      - Space study
        - Collection work areas, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 759)
        - Research facilities, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 760)
      - Risk assessment, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 761)
      - Space planning, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 762)
      - University Space Utilization Survey, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 763)
      - Alterations and work orders, 1989-1994 (Box 12, Folder 764)
      - Compact shelving, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 765)
      - Courtesy storage, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 766)
      - Annex, 1983-1998 (Box 12, Folder 767)
      - Hall of Graduate Studies (HGS), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 768)
      - HGS records storage area, relocation, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 769)
      - Hammond Hall, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 770)
      - Mudd Library, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 771)
      - SML renovation - Meyer Moving and Storage, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 772)
      - Chapel, 1992-1997 (Box 12, Folder 773)
      - Exhibit space, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 774)
      - Processing room, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 775)
      - Off site, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 776)
      - Reading room, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 777)
      - SML vaults, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 778)
      - Science Park, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 779)
    - Technical Services (Systems)
      - 1991 (Box 12, Folder 780)
      - Technical Services meetings, 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 781 - 782)
      - 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 783)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 784)
      - Program definition, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 785)
      - Staffing, circa 1990s (Box 12, Folder 786)
      - Staff Technical Services L1 posting, 1990 June (Box 12, Folder 787)
      - Processing Instructions 1976, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 788)
      - Procedures, 1988-1995 (Box 12, Folder 789)
      - Processing policy, appendices, and procedures, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 790)
      - Calculation of collection size, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 791)
      - Word-processing of finding aids, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 792)
      - PROC code requests, 1985-1990 (Box 12, Folder 793)
      - Ms. Groups being processed, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 794)
      - Collection analysis - TFAC, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 795)
      - Collection analysis and processing plans, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 796)
      - Processing priority system, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 797)
      - Processing plans and progress, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 798)
      - Cataloging and Orbis, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 799)
      - Orbis - MATPS conversion status 34-35, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 800)
    - Personnel
      - Staffing - Reading Room Monitor, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 801)
      - Extreme Weather Guidelines, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 802)
      - Labor Relations, 1989-1993 (Box 12, Folder 803)
      - Part-Time Work Option, 1990-1995 (Box 12, Folder 804)
      - Personnel Information Exchange, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 805)
      - Performance Planning and Assessment Workshop, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 806)
      - Promotion Review, 1988-1995 (Box 12, Folder 807)
      - C/T Job Questionnaire, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 809)
      - Yale University Human Resources Clerical and Technical Position Classification Program, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 810)
      - M/P Questionnaire, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 812)
      - M/P Questionnaire Drafts, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 813)
      - Union, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 815)
      - Shutdown, August, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 816)
      - Contract Negotiations, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 817)
      - Performance goals and objectives, 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 818 - 820)
      - Administrative Assistant temporary reassignment, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 821)
      - Archives Assistant - Technical Services, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 822)
      - Archivist I - Technical Services, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 823)
      - LI Archivist, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 824)
      - LI Recruit, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 825)
      - Cataloging position, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 826)
      - Archivist for Legal Project, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 827)
      - Search - Project Archivist - Presidential records project, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 828)
      - Search - Manager of Systems Records - Management Services, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 829)
      - Reference Assistant, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 830)
      - Temporary Reference Assistant, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 831)
      - Reference Assistant, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 832)
      - Security Monitor, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 833)
      - Technical Services (LIII), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 834)
      - Search - Head of Technical Services, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 835)
      - VAHT Catalog Assistant, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 836)
      - Archives 300
        - Lead Archivist Search, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 837)
        - LII Archivist, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 838)
        - Media and publications archivist, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 839)
        - Archivist I, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 840)
        - Archives Assistants, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 841)
      - Digital Resources Manager, circa 1998 (Box 13, Folder 842)
      - VAHT recruitment, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 843)
      - Manager of reference services, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 844)
      - User support specialist, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 845)
    - Personnel: Staff Files [Restricted until Jan 1, 2074]
      - Woods, Val, circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 894)
  - Numismatics
    - Mailbox inventory, computer file (XML)
    - 1996-1999 (Box 13, Folder 895)
    - Transfer to Yale Art Gallery (YAG), 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 896)
    - Catalogs, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 897)
    - Yale Art Gallery exhibit, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 898)
  - Yale University Library
    - Mailbox inventory, computer file (XML)
    - SML Record Services and Collections, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 899)
    - Divinity Library
      - Luce proposal, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 900)
      - Special Collections, circa 1990s (Box 14, Folder 901)
    - Open Book, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 902)
    - Orbis, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 903)
    - Michael A. Keller (MAK), 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 904 - 905)
    - From Michael A. Keller (MAK) for comment, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 906)
    - Michael A. Keller (MAK) et al. meetings, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 907)
    - YUL -Collection Development, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 908)
    - Committee on Online Scholarly Information (COSI), 1993 (Box 14, Folder 909)
    - ZyIndex, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 910)
    - Yale Factfiles, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 911)
    - Pelikan, J.: Future of the University, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 912)
    - Academic plan "Building on Strength", 1990 (Box 14, Folder 913)
    - University Historian, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 914)
  - Collections collaborative
    - Mailbox inventory, computer file (XML)
  - Connecticut organizations